It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training
to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, they return to the Sabaody Archipelago
and move forward to the next stage of their journey, the New World.
We aren't getting ready to take off, are we?
We're still missing half the crew here.
I mean, did Luffy even make it to the Archipelago yet?
It's all under control.
Captain! Huh? He's a friend of the crew, if you follow. Say hi.
In other words, Luffy arrived earlier this morning.
I gave Sanji a baby transponder snail when he stopped by,
so I'll tell him to come back. You should have Zoro with him, too.
Fine! You wanna fight me?
I've trained these legs on the shores of hell for two years!
Then you better use him to run, cause I will cut you in half!
Good. We should hurry.
Because any moment now, the Navy will be attacking with a sizable force.
Unfortunately, there's no way to contact your captain.
But if you follow this Vivre card, you should be able to hunt him down.
Let's hope the fake straw hats buy you a bit of time.
Grove 42 is on the outskirts, so it's close to the sea.
Take the sunny there and be ready to depart on a moment's notice.
I'm sure you'd like to relax after these two difficult years, but it wasn't meant to be.
The winds of the new world wait for no one.
The battle is on! Show them what you got from training!
That should cover the basics at least, but read this before you set out.
I doubt the coding will give you trouble, but better safe than sorry.
Thanks for the tips. This should be fun.
Do you guys think Luffy grew a big beard or big muscles or something?
Oh man, I bet he looks cool now!
I'm sure he does.
Okay, enough talk. Let's head to Grove 42!
Oh, right. Guess I better give Zoro and Sanji a call then.
I'm worried though.
Huh?
Knowing Luffy, he's probably finding some way to get into trouble as we speak.
It'll be our trouble soon enough. This is gonna be another wild ride, isn't it?
Oh, I have an idea. Let me go pick him up. This will be good, I promise.
If you don't get out of our way, we'll arrest every last one of you!
I'd like to see you try. Just let the man play us rock and roll, dammit!
Hey! What's going on over there?
It's out of control, I'll tell you that much!
The Navy came to arrest Soul King during his show when those fans are rioting!
Looks like he made us escape though!
You skinless traitor! I'm gonna make you pay!
Anyway, that's not the big story here!
Soul King is actually a pirate known as the Humming Swordsman!
He's one of the Straw Hats!
Thank you for the ride, my friend!
And that was impeccable timing, I must say!
You can thank Shockey for putting all this together!
Your friends should be waiting for you at Grove 42!
I'm so eager to see them again, my heart is beating out of my chest!
Kidding! Obviously my chest is an empty void!
Why are they even fighting?
I don't know, but both of them are strong as heck!
Still standing after all of that? Maybe you got stronger after all!
Yeah, and your itty bitty baby attacks actually tickle a little now!
Too bad they still don't hurt as bad as your food hurts my stomach!
You're gonna fight about it!
So here's the skinny, brother!
Luffy's on the island!
Somewhere!
But the Navy's about to close in!
And the rest of the crew is headed to Grove 42!
Meet us there!
Roger that, Frankie!
Click!
What's up?
Great! You mean you weren't listening?
Well, let's see...
Navy!
Come here!
Us pirates!
Ship!
Run away!
Is that clear enough?
Why are you talking like that?
Did you hit your head or something?
Sorry.
I just thought I'd speak on your level for once.
Huh?
Alright then!
After this, stupid cook, die!
Real funny.
Anyway, you know what all that racket over there's about?
Huh?
You.
Right.
Noisy.
There.
Wow!
These guys sure are worked up!
Alright, that's enough yakking!
Listen!
Turns out Sansi and Zoro found one of the guys who insulted me!
In fact, he's here with us right now!
Look at this little punk!
I'm gonna beat a lesson into him with my own two hands!
Cause when you piss me off, then things get ugly!
And let this be a lesson to all of you, too!
If you ever cross me, if you ever disrespect me,
you're gonna end up just like this chump!
Don't forget who's the boss of this crew!
Is that perfectly clear?
Yeah!
But you're in that bounty somehow,
and it wasn't by playing Naisy Nights.
What's with this guy?
Zoro?
Sanji?
A friend of yours or something?
I don't think he likes me.
We've got you surrounded!
Nobody move an inch!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You and the rest of your crew are under arrest!
Surrender immediately!
The Navy?
And don't bother running away!
We've blocked off every exit in Grove 46!
You guys leave with us, or you're gonna leave in a body bag!
But my disguise is perfect!
How did the Navy know I was here?
Why?
Why would you think that this was about you?
Captain, please tell me we're not all dead!
Stop flipping out!
We'll be just fine!
Why do you think we recruited all these guys?
We've got pirates with 100 million bounties here!
But this is scary!
Then sit back and watch!
Caribou, you're up!
Use that marine as a shield and make us a path out of this dump!
Wait, what marine?
We sent a scout here earlier that looks like he was taken captive!
Dammit, that's not good!
Huh?
I didn't quite catch that one, boss!
Wanna run it by me again?
Get with the program!
I said use the captive as a shield and get us out!
What an interesting idea!
You want me to put the poor sinner to use while we still can?
What the hell are you doing, Caribou?
We need him to escape!
Did you even hear me?
Although that would be terribly convenient,
I'm afraid it simply won't do!
Why not?
Because he told me he hadn't called the Navy yet!
And that makes him a filthy little liar!
Caribou, no!
That crazy bastard!
Who's the captain here, dammit?
Oh well, so much for that plan!
You high and mighty types seem to think it's alright to lie to someone if they're a so-called bad guy!
Would I object to that?
I guess they're not surrendering, huh?
Should've figured as much!
George, show the pirates no mercy!
No mercy!
No!
Good luck!
Our boss is Straw Hat Luffy!
He's not gonna lose to a bunch of chumps like you!
Let's go!
If you've got a plan, I'd hurry!
Listen to your captain!
You guys are pissing me off!
The guy just said that I was his boss, but I've never even seen him before!
I do not have time to deal with your nonsense right now!
Aim for their captain in charge!
I know you!
You're lip service Doty!
Your bounty's 88 million!
You may be idiots, but at least you're not cowards!
Don't let him intimidate you!
Holy crap!
He's got a bounty of 92 million!
That's gashed Albion!
We'll take him down!
Justice is on our side!
The ground is soaked with the blood of hypocrites!
Its overwhelming stench makes me so sick!
A 210 million bounty!
Wet-haired caribou!
Huh?
Too late to surrender now!
Oh!
Dammit!
No one said he had a devil fruit power!
Why don't we all slow down a bit?
Haven't you heard that stress can lead to an early grave?
My sword!
Those new recruits aren't half bad!
We got this in a bag!
I told you we'd be fine!
Hey boys!
I got a deal for ya!
Or rather it's a contest to see who can kill the most marines before they run away in terror!
Winner becomes my second mate!
Make those bastards bleed!
Yeah!
What do you mean second mate?
What about us?
I'd think of a way to make myself useful if I were you!
We've got some real heavy hitters on the crew now!
I might actually pull this pirate thing off!
Ha ha ha ha!
What?
Pasa Vistas!
Oh hell!
Nobody told me they were gonna be here!
I kinda wanna beat up those robot guys but Hancock said to stay out of trouble so I guess I won't!
Those things that vaporize the mustache off your stupid face you nutbag!
Monkey D. Luffy has been identified. Commence attack.
Those things are aiming straight at me! Can I even run or am I just dead?
I was hoping I'd get to rumble with them someday!
Lip service Doty identified and subdued. Sustains no damage. Searching for next target.
Captain Doty!
Follow the Pasa Vistas! Capture every pirate in your path!
Doty's that cold!
A bounty like that and these guys took him down in only one shot?
We're screwed!
Hancock wait for us!
I ain't waiting for nobody! The thing took out Doty! I don't see the chance!
Straw Hat, do something! You're the only one who can stop him now!
I hate to beg, Captain, but your whole crew is about to get blown up over here!
There's nowhere left to run!
Aw crap, he's gone!
Where is Straw Hat?
They keep calling for their captain, but...
Go now you guys! My side is killing me!
Go your side! The lasers are gonna kill you!
Get your fat ass out of my way!
Huh? Who is this idiot?
Who is this idiot?
He's here!
Captain Luffy!
This is gonna be good!
You paying attention, Corbool?
No! I was facing out!
Over here, moron! Who are you bowing to it?
Get up, Captain Luffy!
Show him what you're made of!
Would you look at that! Guess we don't have to die after all!
Am I mistaken or did they call you Captain Luffy?
Why wouldn't they call me that? I mean you realize who you're talking to right now, don't you?
Go!
Get out of my way before I grab your intestines and pull them out of your ear!
I'd run if I were you!
You're face to face with the son of Dragon the Revolutionary!
That means I'm the grandson of the Hero Garp!
I stare down the three admirals in the War of the Best!
Oh, and my bounty?
It clocks into 400 million berries!
You're not straw hat, you human pile of garbage! Not even close!
Am I mistaken or did they just call you Captain Luffy?
Why wouldn't they call me that? I mean you realize who you're talking to right now, don't you?
Go!
Get out of my way before I grab your intestines and pull them out of your ear!
I'd run if I were you!
You're face to face with the son of Dragon the Revolutionary!
That means I'm the grandson of the Hero Garp!
I stare down the three admirals in the War of the Best!
Oh, and my bounty?
It clocks into 400 million berries!
I'm-
Turn on straw hat, you human pile of garbage! Not even close!
Huh?
What?!
That guy just took out straw hat!
So that's it.
Fools. They thought that they could join the straw hats and enter the new world.
PX5, who is this imposter?
Confirmed. He is triple-tongued D'Amato Black, a pirate with a 26 million berry bounty.
What?!
Wait, if he's only worth 26 million, that means-
We'll have people free!
Look it, guys! The gig is up!
What the hell are we supposed to do now?
It's bad enough this guy tricked us, but now we got the Navy called on us too!
Guess the real straw hat is dead after all.
What the hell?!
You mean straw hat didn't get fat and gross? This guy was just fat and gross to begin with?!
Wait, what?!
That fat gross guy was pretending to be me?!
That's Sanji and Zoro!
They looked real, but I guess they were fakes too!
Wow, this is blowing my mind. I gotta get out of here.
I know you aren't real straw hats and you're just victims of this fool, but you're still pirates.
That means a lot of you are coming with us!
And although I cannot imagine why, the real straw hat is here somewhere too.
When we entered the area, PX5 detected him on the stage with the imposters.
Fire on straw hat, PX5!
That was close!
You almost blew up all my lunches! What did food ever do to you?!
Uh...
Huh?
It's... it's really him, isn't it?
That straw hat looting!
The real straw hat was here and we didn't even know!
Nothing has changed, men!
We came here to capture straw hat and that's what we're doing!
So there you are!
I had enough of you the last time we fought!
I'm just trying to set sail! I'm not supposed to start any trouble!
Oh, it's no trouble! But you won't be setting sail!
Unlike two years ago, I'm an official Navy officer now!
That means I'm taking you in if it's the last thing I do!
PX5 fire!
Is that all?
What?
All those together then, there's a long belly.
I'm playing in to the next level!
Good job!
Ah really?
I forgot about those who are just athletes around this game.
Yes, of course.
My деся
This is worse than I thought. He can use Haki now.
He made a passive beast and all it took was one horse!
So long! Though I have a feeling I'm gonna see you again somewhere!
Get back here and fight me!
Don't let him go, man! Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Buffy! Luffy! Shoulda knows!
All I had to do was follow the explosions and I knew I'd find you!
Okay, it's you for real this time!
And Zora's not even fat! Way to go!
Roronoa and Blackfoot! I should have known they were still alive!
R.I.P. at seven attack!
Huh?
I'm the one who got him!
Keep dreaming! My kick broke his neck!
and my kick broke his neck!
Ahh!
It's a real strong hit!
They're monsters!
The big ones were nothing like this at all!
By the way, Luffy, you're number nine.
Nobody cares! Would you give up on that?
Everyone's waiting at the sunny. Let's get moving.
Got it!
We're not missing this chance!
Every last Marine! After them!
Yes, sir!
Man, it's been forever, huh?
I bet everyone's so cool now!
I can't wait to see!
What happened? Let's go!
Rally!
It can't be!
That's Star King's Rally!
I came to check on you, but it seems you have this under control.
In fact, you're even stronger than when I left you.
Huh?
Finally time to see your friends. You've been waiting for long enough.
Me?
Thanks, Rally! For real! You did so much for me these past two years!
Ha ha! No need to get sappy on me. Just go.
Hmm?
One last thing!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates! You hear me?
I've got a touch!
I'm gonna be some crying.
I said, no NEIL
Is that DOUGLAY
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I said, no NEIL
This is a pick first.
We go!
After two long years and one chaotic afternoon,
the Straw Hats are finally ready to renew their voyage.
However, before they can set off to Fishman Island,
they must contend with a massive Navy force determined to stop them.
Fortunately, they returned to Sabaori with some powerful friends.
On the next One Piece, everyone together!
Luffy's setting out for the new world!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!